Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Speyer, James (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Emergency, 1920 Dec. 31
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1923 Jan. 3; 6p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1923 Jan. 18; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1923 Feb. 6; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1925 Dec. 2; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1925 Dec. 3; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1927 Dec. 20; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1928 Apr. 3; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1931 May 29; 1p
    - Society for German and Austrian science and art, 1933 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Germanistic Society of Amer., 1920 Feb.; 2p
      Also see Hepburn, A. Burton; Herman A. Metz; Schurz, Carl L.
    - From Paul, Hans, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p
  - Spice, Allan M. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 5; 1p
  - Spicer, John O. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 19
    - To Boas, 1885 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 May 2
  - Spier, Erna Gunther (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 27; 4p
    - See Boas to, 1922 Dec. 10; 4p
    - Spier (Mrs.Ernag), 1923 Jan. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 2p
  - Spier, Leslie (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 24
    - To Boas, 1917 June 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 July 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 14; 6p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 NOv. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1936 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 11; 1p
    - see Boas, F., 1938 Jan.
    - open letter on culture and democracy in Spain, Replies, 1938 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 27; 2p
  - Spiess, Joseph (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 22; 1p
  - Spinden, E. S. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 17; 1p
  - Spinden, Herbert J. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 2
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1923 June; 2p
  - Spingarn, A. B. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 11; 1p
    - From Bryan, H.R., 1933 Jan. 5
    - Enc. with Bryan, H.R., 1933 Jan. 6
  - Spitz, L. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 23; 1p
  - Spitz, William (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1887 May 30
    - To Boas, 1887 May 30
  - Spitzer, Robert (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 May 20; 1p
    - see Boas, F. (to Spitzer, R.), 1942 May 25
  - Spitzger, E. A. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 23; 1p
  - Spitzka, E. A. (Box 84)
    - To Boas, 1903 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 25; 1p
  - Spivack, Robert G. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 July 8; 1p
    - Enc. Spivack, R.G. (to Razovsky, C.), 1938 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 4; 2p
    - To Razovsky, C., 1938 July 8; 2p
    - Enc. with Spivack, R.G., 1938 July 8
    - To Razovsky, C., 1938 July 8; 2p
    - Enc. with Razovsky, C., 1938 July 22
  - Sprague, L. W. (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 24
  - Spreyer & Co. (Box 84)
    See Pendreigh, F.
  - Spring, Josephine (Box 84)
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Springer, J. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 2p
  - Sproul, R. G. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 6
  - Spun (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 6
  - Spurgeon, J. J. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 7
  - Staats-Herold Corporation (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Staatszeitung (Box 85)
    - Bericht ueber den "Deutscher Tag" des Kultur verbandes., 1939 Dec. 4
      Enc. Lips, J.E. (toSattler, Otto)
  - Stabel, Dr. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 19; 1p
      (see also Staebel)
  - Stacpole, F. A. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 22; 1p
  - Stackpole, S. H. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 7
  - Stadtmüller, Norbert (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 2p
  - Staebel (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 11; 1p
    - Enc. with Reinhardt, G.P., 1933 Sep. 12
      (see also StC$bel)
  - Stake, William & Co. (Box 85)
    - Fom Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - Fom Boas, 1907 May 1
    - Fom Boas, 1907 May 4
    - Fom Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
    - Fom Boas, 1910 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 May 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 July 15
    - To Boas, 1910 July 29
  - Stalesoski, A. von (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 27; 4p
  - Stalewer, von (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 2
  - Staley, M. L. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 12; 1p
  - Stalpnagil (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 16
  - Stamp, J. Harley (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 2; 2p
  - Standard, P. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Standardization of Technique in Physical Anthropology (Box 85)
    - see Reichert, E., 1935 Sept. 9
  - Leland Stanford University (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 14
  - Stang, Frederick (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 6p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 28; 1p
    - Enc: Gallimard, G. (to Stang, K.), 1936 Mar. 3
    - Stang, F. (to Librairie Gallimard, 1936 Mar. 28
    - From Gallimard, G., 1936 Mar. 3
    - Enc. with Stang, F., 1936 Mar. 28
    - To Librairie Gallimard, 1936 Mar. 28; 1p
    - Enc. with Stang, F., 1936 Mar. 28
    - To Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, 1926 Apr. 12; 11p
    - From Ruml, B., 1926 June 11
    - From Gallimard Gaston, 1935 Dec. 12; 1p
    - Enc. with letter to F. Boas from Gaston Gallimard, 1936 Jan. 24
  - Stangeland, C. E. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 8
  - Stanley, A. A. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 9
  - Stanley, Jean (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Stanley, Louise (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Stanton, F.L. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
  - Stapelfeldt, Karsten (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 20
  - Stark, J. (Box 85)
    - The pragmatic and the dogmatic spirit in physics, 1938 Apr. 30; 3p
  - Starr, Frederick (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1896 July 18
    - To Boas, 1896 July 31
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 1p
  - Starr, H. M. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 16; 1p
  - Starreluas, F. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept 5
  - Statement of Allotments and Expenditures, 1913-1914 (Box 85)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1914, 1p
  - Stauffer, R. E. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Stauterr, A. W. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 2
  - Stechert, C. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 10; 2p
  - Stechert, G. E. & Co. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1906 June 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 June 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 7; 1p
    - see: Stechert, G.E. & Co. to Andrews, H.A., 1920 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 18; 1p
    - Enc. Puckett, N.N. (to Stechert, G.E. and Co.)
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 17
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 27; 1p
    - To Andrews, H.A., 1920 June 3; 1p
    - From Bloomfield, L., 1926 Nov. 4
    - From Meyerhoffer, Marie, 1921 Oct. 21; 2p
    - Enc. with letter ot Boas, F. from Meyerhoffer, Marie, 1921 Oct. 26
    - From O'Flynn, A.C., 1923 Jan.; 2p
    - From Puckett, N.N.
    - Enc. with Stechert, G.E. and C., 1924 Nov. 18
    - From Steinen, K. von den, 1923 Feb. 25; 2p
    - From Wülfing, John, 1922 Aug. 22; 2p
    - From Wülfing, John, 1922 Sep. 2; 1p
  - Steedman, Elsie V. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 18; 2p
  - Steel, J. H. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 28; 1p
    - Enc. Open letter, 1938 Mar. 17; 1p
      re Fascism
  - Steen, Elizabeth (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 7; 1p
  - Steenitzer, Alfred (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 3
  - Stefansson, V. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 15; 4p
    - Enc: The Woman who married a Dog, 1926 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
    - To Conklin, E.G, 1942 Oct. 29; 2p
  - Steffens, L. (Box 85)
    - see Boas, F. (to Curtis, C.), 1933 Feb. 27
    - see Boas, F. (to Garner, J.N.), 1933 Feb. 27
    - see Boas, F. (to Walsh, T.J.), 1933 Feb. 27
  - Stegesmundt (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 18; 3p
      Enc. Das Fehlen der amerikanischen Literatur in Deutschen
  - Steichmann, H. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 24; 1p
  - Stein (Box 85)
    - To Dr. Correns, 1924 July 22
  - Stein, Fred (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 26; 1p
  - Stein, F. M. (Box 85)
    - To Wallerstein, L., 1933 Oct. 17; 1p
    - Enc. with Wallerstein, Leo, 1933 Oct. 18
  - Stein, Robert (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1892 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1893 July 20
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 28
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1896 May 14
    - To Boas, 1896 May 15
    - To Boas, 1896 May 21
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 16
  - Stein, T. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1929 June 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 25
  - Steinberg, S. H. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1934 June 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 7; 1p
  - Steinen, Diether v. d. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 23; 2p
    - Found at end of Nov. 1937, 4p
    - see Kroeber, A.L., 1938 May 23
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 22; 2p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1938, 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 26; 2p
    - Found at end of Dec.
      see Boas, F. (to Dunn, L.C.)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939, 1940 Mar. 11; 2p
    - To Kroeber, A.L., 1937 Nov. 12; 2p
      Enc: Steinen, D.v.d. Vita, publications, and plan of book
    - Found in enc. Kroeber, A.L., 1938 Jan. 14
  - Steinen, Erika v.d. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Nov. 1937, 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 2p
  - Steinen, Helmut v.d. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1932 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 6; 2p
  - Steinen, Karl v.d. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1903 July 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 5p
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 May 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 July 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept.19
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 June 22
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 June 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 10; 3p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Nov. 27; 4p
    - To Boas, 1895 May 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1897 Aug. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Apr. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 23; 3p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 June 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 July 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 6
    - To Boas, 1905 July 7
    - To Boas, 1905 July 24; 4p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 July 25
    - To Boas, 1908 July 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1915 June 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 July 14; 8p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 11
    - To Boas, 1923 July 17
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 2; 5p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 17; 2p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Schmidt-Ott, F.), 1926 Mar. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 2p
    - To Boas n.y. "Mittw.", 1928 Dec.; 2p.
    - From Loubat, J.F. duc de
    - Found at end of Oct. 1902
    - To Gregory, H.E., 1921 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Stechert, G.E., 1923 Feb. 25; 2p
  - Steinen, Wolfrum v.d. (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p
    - Enc. Boas, F. (to Schuchhardt, C.), 1939 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 9 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 July 20
    - To Boas, 1907 July 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Steiner, F. B. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 8; 1p
  - Steiney, Lore v. d. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 19
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 21; 8p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 4; 5p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 15; 4p